(没有汽油)
小姑娘
Little girl?
我是警察
I'm a policeman.
小姑娘
Little girl.
不要怕　好吗
Don't be afraid, OK?
小姑娘
Little girl.
《行尸走肉》
男女之间有什么差别
What's the difference between men and women?
-你开玩笑吗　-不　认真的
- Is this a joke? - No, serious.
我从没见过一个女人懂得关灯
I never met a woman who knew how to turn off a light.
她们生来只知道开灯　从来不懂关灯
They're born thinking the switch only goes one way.
她们一离开一个房间就会被“闪瞎”
They're struck blind the second they leave a room.
每个我曾给过家里钥匙的女人都这样　我发誓
I mean every woman, I ever let have a key, I swear to God.
比方说我一到家　整栋房子灯火通明
It's like I... come home, house all lit up,
而我的任务呢　显而易见…
and my job, apparently because...
因为我是男性
because my chromosomes happen to be different
所以我得跑遍整栋房子
cause I then gotta walk through that house,
把所有她没关的灯全关了
turn off every single light this chick left on.
-是么　-当然了　哥们
- Is that right? - Yeah, baby.
好吧　肖恩神父要开始布道了
Alright, Reverend Shane's preaching to you now, boy.
就是那个小妞
The same chick, mind ya.
又在念叨全球变暖问题
She'll bitch about global warming.
肖恩神父要开始
You see, this is -- this is when Reverend Shane wants to
引用盖伊福音了
quote from the Guy Gospel and say "Um, darling?"
“亲爱的　要是你和这星球上的其他小妞”
"maybe you, and every other pair of boobs on this planet
“懂得开了灯就要关”
just figured out that the light switch see, goes both ways,"
“那全球变暖可能就没这么严重了”
maybe we wouldn't have so much global warming."
-你这么说吗　-对
- You say that? - Yeah.
不管怎样　还算很客气
Anyway, uh... Polite version...
但结果呢
Still man, that... that earns me this.
她丢给你一副厌恶的嘴脸　你肯定想像不到
This look and loathing you would not believe.
驱魔人一般的声音蹦出来
And that's when the exorcist voice pops out.
“你怎么跟我那该死的老爸似的”
"You sound just like my damn father.
“总是唠叨电费”
"Always,always yelling about the power bill,"
“要我关灯”
"telling me to turn off the damn lights."
你怎么说
What do you say to that?
我知道我想说什么
You know what I wanna say.
我想说　“贱人”
I wanna say,"Bitch, you mean to tell me
“原来早就有人和你说过了”
you've been hearing this your entire　life
“你却还是蠢到学不会关灯”
"and you are still too damn stupid to learn how to turn off a switch?
其实我没有这么说
You know... I don't actually say that,tho.
-那样就惨了　-用那种
- That would be bad. - Yeah, go with the uh...
客气的说法
the polite version there...
-还真明智　-可不是　长官
- Very wise. - Yes, sir.
你和洛莉怎么样了　伙计
So how's it with Lori, man?
她很不错　懂得关灯
She's good. She's good at turning off lights.
真不错
Really good.
不知道为何我们还是会怀疑
I don't know why sometimes we guess.
我也不想
Not what I meant.
我们处得不太好
We didn't have a great night.
听着　伙计　我可能是缺乏幽默感　但我会尽力
Look, man, I may have a... fail to amuse with my sermon, but I did try.
至少你能说说话
The least you could do is speak.
她总这么说　“说话”
That's what she always says: "Speak".
“说话”
"Speak".
她这么说我还保持缄默
You think I was the most closed mouth
你大概觉得我逊毙了
son of a bitch you'd ever hear to hear her tell it.
你有说过你的想法么
Do you express your thoughts?
有分享过你的感受之类的么
You share your feelings and that kind of stuff?
问题是
The thing is...
不管我怎么尝试
lately whenever I try...
她都很不耐烦　好像她根本不想听
everything I say makes her impatient,like she didn't want to hear it after all.
感觉就好像…
It's like she's...
她总会无缘无故地生我气
pissed at me all the time, and I don't know why.
听着　伙计　夫妻间都会这样
Look, man, that's just shit couples go through.
总得经历这段时期
Nah, it's... It's a phase.
知道她今早说的最后一句话吗
Last thing she said this morning?
她说“有时我甚至怀疑你根本不在乎我们”
Sometimes I wonder if you even care about us at all.
她当着孩子的面就这么说
She said that in front of our kid.
想想看他去学校后会怎么想
Imagine going to school with that in your head.
男女之间的区别吗
Difference between men and women?
我绝不会对她说这么残酷的话
I would never say something that cruel to her.
尤其是在卡尔面前
Certainly not in front of Carl.
所有空闲单位　林肯县发生高速追捕
All available units, high speed pursuit
请即刻到现场增援
in progress Lincoln county units request local assistance.
18号公路以南 GTAAD记录217-243以西
Highway 18 south GTAAD W217-243.
高度戒备
Proceed with extreme caution.
嫌犯为两名高加索白人
Suspects are two male Caucasians.
通知各单位　嫌犯已向警方开火
Be advised, they have fired on police officers.
一位林肯县警受伤
One Lincoln county officer is wounded.
一组和三组注意
Unit 1, Unit 3.
85州际公路以西2英里处
18, 2 miles west of Interstate 85
使用林肯县警无线电保持联络
and we'll patch in Linclon County Sheriff radio.
收到　还有5分钟赶到18号公路口
Roger that. We're 5 minutes out on the route 18 intersection.
一组三组注意　到达现场后设立路障
Dispatch, Unit 1, Unit 3, we are 10-97 in code 100.
85州际公路　18号公路　请下达指令
Highway 18, 85 Interstate, please advise.
听着像是那些蠢货被追得东逃西窜
Sounds like they're chasing those idiots up and down every back road we got.
我们可得拍个录像传网上去
Hey, we'll get them on one of those video shows, you know,
弄个“最疯狂警匪追逐”视频　你觉得呢
like World's craziest police chases, what do you think?
我觉得你该专心点　里昂
What I think, Leon, is that you need to stay focused.
别被迎面来的子弹给崩了
Make sure you got a round in the chamber and your safety off.
那样视频可就拉风得多了
Would be kind of cool to get on one of them shows.
真他妈见鬼
Holy shit.
-小心有枪　-放下枪
- Gun, gun, gun. - Put it down!
快放下枪
Put the gun down!
-瑞克　-我没事
- Rick! - I'm alright!
我看到你被击中了　吓死我了
I saw you get tagged, man, it scared the hell out of me.
我也是
Me too.
那见鬼丫的居然开枪打我
Son of a bitch shot me.
你相信么
You believe that?
到时给你件新防弹衣
We'll get you a new vest.
可不是
Yeah.
肖恩　你可不能告诉洛莉
Shane, you do not tell Lori that happened.
绝对不行
Ever.
你明白吗
You understand...
瑞克　不　不要
Rick! Rick! No, no, no!
不　他受伤了
No, no, no, no... He's hurt!
里昂
Leon!
快去叫救护车
You get that ambulance down here,
快去叫救护车　说有警官受伤　快去
you tell them there's an officer down, you do it now!
你看着我　保持清醒　好吗
Shh, shh, shh, hey, you look at me, stay with me, you hear me?
没事　保持清醒　听见了吗
Okay. Shh, shh, stay with me, you hear me?
好吗　保持清醒
Shh, shh, ok? You stay with me, ok?
伙计　我们还在这里
Hey, bud... We're still here.
每天都在
We're still hanging in.
听着　我很抱歉　伙计
Look, I'm sorry, man.
我每次来你都是这副德行
I'm mean watching the same crap every time I come in here.
这是大家一起买的…
Everybody pitched in on these. They uh...
他们要我带过来　致以他们的问候…
They wanted me to bring them down, they send their love and they just...
他们希望你快点好起来
They hope you come back real soon.
总台的琳达和戴安　这是她们选的
Linda and Diane from dispatch, they picked these out.
你应该能看出来吧
You probably could tell, hmm?
我就放在桌上了　好吗
I'll just set this on your side table, ok?
这还不是一般的花瓶
That vase has something special.
老实说
Fess up.
你是不是从吉恩奶奶家偷来的
Did you steal it from your Grandma Gene's house.
但愿你没碰她收藏的汤匙
I hope you left her that spoon collection.
肖恩
Shane?
肖恩　你在厕所吗
Shane, you in the john?
护士　快来
Nurse, help.
护士　来帮帮我
Nurse. Help!
(不要开门　里面有僵尸)
洛莉
Lori!
卡尔　卡尔
Carl! Carl!
洛莉　卡尔
Lori! Carl!
这是真的吗
Is this real?
我真的在这吗
Am I here?
醒过来
Wake, wake up!
爸爸
Daddy, daddy!
卡尔
Carl... Carl?
-我找到你了…　-爸爸　我搞定这混球了
- I found you... - Daddy, I got this sumbitch.
我要敲死他
I'm gonna smack him dead.
他说什么了吗
He say something?
我好像听见他说了什么
I thought I heard him say something.
-他叫我卡尔　-孩子　你也知道他们不说话
- He called me Carl. - Son, you know they don't talk.
先生　你为什么绑着绷带
Hey, mister! What's that bandage for?
-什么　-你受了什么伤
- What? - What kind of wound?
快回答我　见鬼的
You answer me, damn you!
你受了什么伤
What's your wound?
快说
You tell me!
不然我就杀了你
Or I will kill you.
我们帮你换了绷带
Got that bandage changed out.
已经脏得不行了
It was pretty rank.
那个伤
What was?
是什么伤
The wound?
-枪伤　-枪伤
- Gun shot. - Gun shot?
还有其他什么吗
What else? Anything?
光是枪伤还不够惨吗
Gun shot ain't enough?
听好了　我问你答　规矩知不知道
Look, I ask and you answer, It's common courtesy, right?
你有没被咬
Did you get bit?
-咬　-咬
- Bit? - Bit.
咬过　还是被抓过
Chewed. Maybe scratch?
任何诸如此类
Anything like that.
没　我被枪打了
No,I got shot.
就我所知　只有枪伤
Just shot, as far as I know.
让我量下
Hey... Just let me...
感觉凉多了
Feels cooler now.
发烧的话你这会就没命了
Fever would have killed you by now.
我觉得我没有烧
I don't think I have one.
那是你运气好
Be hard to miss.
好好看看这刀有多锋利
Take a moment, eh? Look how sharp it is.
你要做傻事　我就用这个杀了你　我说到做到
You try anything... I will kill you with it,and don't you think I won't.
等你能动弹了就下床
Come on up when you're able.
走
Come on.
这里是弗雷和辛迪·德雷克的家
This place... It's Fred and Cindy Drake's.
从没见过
Never met them.
我来过　这是他们的家
I've been here.This is their place
我们到时就没人
It was empty when we got here.
别动它
Don't do that.
他们被光引过来
They'll see the light.
他们的数量比平时更多了
There's more of them out there than usual.
之前我真不该开枪
I never should have fired that gun today.
枪声把他们都引来了　现在满大街都是
The sound draws them,now they're all over the street.
真蠢啊　居然用枪
Stupid... using a gun...
一切都发生得太快
It all happened so fast...
-我都没想　-你今天枪杀了个人
- I didn't think. - You shot that man today.
人
Man?
不系淫
No man...
你刚说的那是什么浑话
What the hell was that out of your mouth just now?
-那不是个人　-你用枪打了他
- It wasn't a man. - You shot him.
就大街上　门口　有个人
In this street,out front,a man.
看来你要戴眼镜了　那是行尸
For him, you need glasses, that was a walker.
得
Come on.
坐下　别摔了
Sit down,before you fall down.
给　吃吧
Here. Eat.
爸爸　祷告
Daddy... Blessing...
哦对
Yeah.
天上的父　我们衷心赞美您赐予我们食物…
Father,we thank thee for this food... Thy blessings...
祈求您在天上　庇佑我们熬过这疯狂的时日
We ask you to watch over us in these crazy days.
-阿门　-阿门
- Amen. - Amen.
这位先生　你究竟知不知道外面发生了什么
Hey, mister, do you even know what is going on?
我今天刚醒
I woke up today.
在医院里
In a hospital.
然后回到家　就这些
Came home, that's all I know.
-但你不知道那些死人吧　-不　我看见很多
- But you know about the dead people, right? - Yeah, I saw a lot of that.
装卸区遍地都是　还有卡车上
Out on the loading dock, hauling trucks.
不不不　不是这些死了的　是那些还在走的
No... Not the one's they put down... The one's they didn't.
行尸
The walkers.
就像我今天开枪放倒的那个
Like the one I shot today.
因为他就要扒了你
Cause he would have ripped into you.
要吃了你　至少从你身上挖块肉
Try to eat you, take him some flesh at least.
如果这是你头一回听说　我知道听起来肯定很…
But I guess if this is the first you're hearing, I know how it must sound...
-他们都在外面的大街上吗　-对
- They're out there now, in the street? - Yeah.
有时他们在夜里反而更活跃
They're even more active after dark sometimes.
或许是气温低了　该死　估计还是我白天拿枪惹得祸
Maybe it's the cool air or... Hell, maybe it's just me firing up that gun today.
但只要我们保持安静就很安全
But we'll be fine long as we stay quiet.
到早上就应该都走光了
Probably wander off by morning.
听好
Well,listen...
我就说一件事　别被咬
One thing I do know... Don't you get bit!
我们那会看见你的绷带　所以才怕的
We saw your bandage and that's why we were afraid of.
咬一口就能要你的命
Bites kill you.
那烧　能直接把你给烧化了
The fever... burns you out.
可再过那么一会
But then after a while...
你就又活过来了
You come back.
亲眼见过
Seen it happen...
好了
Come on...
卡尔　是你儿子吗
Carl... He your son?
威廉　他今天说过这名字
William. He said his name today...
他还小　比你儿子还小
He's a little younger... than your boy.
跟他妈妈在一起吗
And he's with his mother?
我希望是
I hope so.
-爸　-嗯
- Dad? - Yeah?
问过他了没
Did you ask him?
你的枪伤　我跟我儿子打了个小赌
Your gun shot... We got a little bet going.
我儿子说你是个抢银行的
My boy say you're a... bank robber...
还真猜中了
Yeah...That's me.
就像狄灵杰·卡普(银行抢劫犯)一样
Deadly as Dillinger Kapow.
其实我是县警
Sheriff's deputy
没事的　爸爸在
Hey, it's ok, daddy's here.
没什么
It's nothing.
肯定是当中一个撞到了辆车
One of them must've bumped a car...
你肯定吗
You sure?
以前出过这事
Happened once before.
响了一阵
Went off a few minutes.
熄灯去　德韦恩
Get the light,Dwayne.
就那辆蓝的　街那头
It's the blue one, down the street.
跟上次一样
Same one as last time.
我觉得我们没事
I think we're ok.
那个动静　会不会把他们都招来
That noise... Will it bring more of them?
现在什么都做不了
Nothing to do about it now.
只有等到明天他们都散了
Just have to wait 'em out till morning.
她在那儿
She's here.
别看
Don't look.
离窗子远点
Get away from the windows.
我说了赶紧走　快
I said go! Come on!
好了 安静
Come on, quiet.
好了　给
It's ok, here.
抱着枕头哭吧
Cry into the pillow.
记得不
Can you remember?
她
She, uh...
她在另一间屋里死了　就在床上
She died in the other room, on that bed...
我什么都做不了　那个烧…
Nothin' I can do about it here... That fever, man...
她的皮肤烫得跟火炉似的
Her skin gave off heat like a furnace...
我早该放倒她的　但是…
Should have put her down, I should have put her down, I know that, but...
我就是下不了决心…
You know what... I just didn't have it in me...
她是我儿子他娘亲啊
She's the mother of my child.
你肯定吗　他们都死了
You sure? They're dead.
必须得问　至少得再问一次
They have to ask, at least one more time.
他们都死了
They're dead.
除了脑里边还有点东西
Except for something in the brain.
这就是为什么必须打头
That's why it's gotta be the head.
没事吧
You alright?
让我喘口气
Need a moment
他们还活着
They're alive.
我老婆和儿子
My wife and son.
至少走的时候还活着
At least they were when they left.
你怎么知道
How can you know?
看看这地方
By the look of this place...
卧室里有空的抽屉
I found empty drawers in the bedroom.
他们带了衣服　不多
They packed some clothes.Not a lot.
但是足够路上用
But enough to travel.
也可能是有人闯进来偷走了吧
You know anybody could've broken in here and stolen clothes, right?
看见那些墙上的相框了么
You see the framed photos on the walls?
我就没见
Neither do I.
哪个小偷会要那个
Some random thief took those too, you think?
我的照片簿　全家福　都没了
My photo albums, family pictures, all gone.
相册
Photo albums...
我老婆　也是一个样
My wife... Same thing...
我当时在收拾生存装备　她却拿什么相册
Here I am, packing survival gear, she's grabbing photo albums....
我估计他们会在亚特兰大
They're in Atlanta, I'll bet.
对了
That's right.
-为什么是那　-避难所
- Why there? - Refugee settle.
很大　至少广播停掉前一直这么说
Huge, when they said it, before the broadcast stopped.
军方保护　有吃　有住　他们让人们去那
Military protection food, shelter... They told people to go there.
说是最安全的地方
Said to be safest.
加上他们还有看病的地方
Plus they got that disease place.
疾控中心
Center for Disease Control.
说他们正在想办法解决问题
Said they were working on how to solve this thing.
油和电大概一个月前就都停了
Gas and light have been down for maybe a month.
警局有自备的丙烷系统
Station got its own propane system.
设备还管用
Pilot's still on.
哦上帝啊
Oh, my Lord.
热水耶
Hot water!
感觉爽吧
That feels good, right?
来啊　来啊　来啊　来
Bring it, bring it bring it around ahah
你说啥
what did you say what
德韦恩　去后面那间屋子换衣服
Dwayne... Dress in room back there.
-你该说什么　德韦恩　-谢谢
- What would you say, Dwayne? - Thank you.
看来亚特兰大是个好去处
Atlanta sounds like a good deal.
安全　还有人…
Safer anyway. People...
我们原本就是要去那里
That's where we were heading.
一切都乱了套
Things got crazy.
你根本就无法想像
Man, you won't believe.
恐慌蔓延…
The panic...
街上根本过不去　然后我们…
Streets won't fit to be on, and then we'll...
我妻子　走不动
My wife... couldn't travel.
跟不上队伍　因此我们得找个藏身之处
No, not with our herds, so we had to find a place to lay low.
她死了之后…
And then,after she died...
我们就在这里徘徊不前
We just stayed hunkered down.
我想我们只是不舍得离开
I guess we just froze in place.
有离开这里的计划吗
Plan to move on?
目前没这打算
Haven't worked up to it yet.
这里的枪少了不少
A lot of it's gone missing.
老爸　我能学习开枪吗
Dad, can I learn to shoot?
我已经不小了
I'm old enough.
废话　当然得学
Hell yes you're going to learn.
我得好好教你　万万不能掉以轻心
We gotta do it carefully, teach you to respect the weapon.
没错　这可不是玩具枪
That's right. It's not a toy.
扣动扳机是一件很严肃的事
You pull the trigger, you have to mean it.
切记在心　德韦恩
Always remember that, Dwayne.
是　长官
Yes, sir.
给
Here.
拿着
Go on.
带着这把枪
Take that one.
没什么特别之处
Nothing fancy.
不过瞄准精确高
Scope's accurate.
节约弹药
Conserve your ammo.
弹药用起来比你想像得要快　尤其是打靶练习时
Goes faster than you think. Especially at target practice.
德韦恩
Dwayne.
-啥事　-把这个放车里
- Yeah? - Take this to the car.
你们真的不跟我一起走
You sure you won't come along?
过些日子再说
A few more days...
等德韦恩学会了开枪　我也振作了精神
By the end, Dwayne will know how to shoot and I won't be so rusty.
你也带着一个吧
You got one better.
每天黎明时分　我的会开上几分钟
I'll turn mine on, a few minutes every day at dawn.
你们到那时　通过这个联系我
You get up there, that's how you find me.
你认为他们也在那里吗
You think they're here?
以防万一　小心不为过
Can't afford not to. Not anymore.
听着　记住这一点
Look, just one thing.
他们一般不会单独出动
They may not seem like much one at a time...
而是一群群似饿虎般地蜂拥而来
but in a group all round up and hungry...
兄弟　千万要小心
Man, you watch your ass.
你们也是
You too.
瑞克　你真是个好人
You a good man, Rick.
希望你们一家能团聚
I hope you find your wife and son.
后会有期　德韦恩
Be seeing you, Dwayne.
照顾好你老爸
Take care of your old man.
是　长官
Yes, sir.
里昂·贝西
Leon Bessi?
他给我的印象不好
Didn't think much of him.
又粗心又蠢　但我不能放任不管
Careless and dumb, but... can't leave him like this.
你知道他们会听到枪声的吧
You know, if they hear the shot.?
那就趁他们出现前　赶紧闪人
Let's not be here when they show up.
我们走吧　儿子　快
Let's go, son. Come on.
你在这看会漫画
Read your comic books a while.
我去楼上
Daddy'll be upstairs.
爸爸
Daddy?
没关系　德韦恩
It's alright, Dwayne.
儿子　你待在下面　别上来
You stay there, son. Don't come up here.
来啊　宝贝
Come on, baby.
很遗憾你变成这样
I'm sorry this happened to you.
加油　你能行的
Come on, come on.
紧急频道呼叫中
Broadcasting on emergency channel.
我们正沿着85号洲际公路开往亚特兰大
We'll be approaching Atlanta on Highway 85.
收到请回话
Anybody reads, please respond.
喂　有人吗
Hello. Hello.
有没有人听得到我的声音
Can anybody hear my voice?
有人在听吗　收到请回话
Anybody out there? Anybody hears me, please respond.
喂　听得到我的声音吗
Hello, can you hear my voice?
有人吗　可以听到我的声音吗
Hello? Hello? Can anybody hear my voice?
可以　我可以听到
Yes, I can hear you.
你要过来了　完毕
You're coming through. Over.
听到请回话
Anybody who reads, please respond.
紧急频道呼叫中
Broadcasting on emergency channel.
我们正沿着85号洲际公路开往亚特兰大
We'll be approaching Atlanta on Highway 85.
收到请回话
Anybody reads, please respond.
我们就在城外
We're just outside the city.
该死
Damn it.
喂　喂
Hello? Hello?
他听不到我的声音　我没办法提醒他
He couldn't hear me. I couldn't warn him.
用无线电再联系他试试
Try to raise him again.
过来　孩子　这玩意你最拿手了
Come on, son. You know best how to work this thing,
喂　呼叫人还在吗
Hello, hello, is the person who calls still on the air?
我是肖恩·威尔士警官
This is officer Shane Walsh,
呼叫不明人士　请回话
broadcasting a person unknown, please respond.
他不在了
He's gone.
还有人还活着
There are others.
不只有我们
It's not just us.
是啊　意料之中
Yeah, We knew there would be, right,
因此民用波段电台才一直开着
that's why we let the CB on.
这电台的确挺有用处
A lot of good it's been doing.
我们应该在85号公路上放些标志
And I've been saying for a week,
来提醒人们远离城里
we ought to put signs up on 85
这话我都说了一星期了
to warn people away from the city.
人们不知道如今城里已是行尸的天下
Folks got no idea what they're getting into.
我们没有足够的时间
We don't have enough time.
我们得腾出时间来
I think we need to make time.
这个…　这一点我们无能为力
Yeah, that, uh... That's a luxury we can't afford.
我们有幸活下来　活一天算一天
We are surviving here. We are day to day.
那你建议派谁去
And who the hell would you propose to send?
我去　给我辆车
I'll go. Give me a vehicle.
你知道谁都不准单独行动
Nobody goes anywhere alone, you know that.
是　长官
Yes, sir.
停　别跟上　过去坐下　孩子
Hey, hey, hey, come on, take a sit, buddy.
没事　去吧　没事的
You're alright, go on, you're alright.
怎么　在生我的气吗
What, you're pissed at me?
你再怎么气　也改变不了什么
Well pissing me all you want won't gonna change anything.
我不会让你陷于险境
I'm not putting you in danger, okay?
无论如何都不会
I'm not doing it for anything.
我知道有时候
I make you feel like
你很想扇我耳光…
sometimes you wanna slap me outside the head...
我就直说了吧　美女
I'll tell you what, girl.
你想扇的话　别客气　尽管扇
You feel that need, you go right ahead.
我人就在这
I'm right here.
你不能总这样气冲冲地半路走掉
You cannot walk off like that, all half-cocked.
你若不想为你我放弃这念头的话
Look, if you don't wanna do it for my sake or for your sake,
这我管不着
that's fine.
但是　为了他你就好好待着吧
But just... You do it for him.
你儿子经历了太多
That boy has been through too much.
他不能再失去他的妈妈　好吗
And he's not losing his mother too, ok?
-好　-好　好吧
- Okay. - Ok, fine.
你自己答应了
You tell me okay.
不难吧
It's not hard.
妈妈
Mom?
小鬼　她在里面　进去吧
What's up, buddy? She's in there, go on.
我不想让你担心
I don't want you to worry.
我哪儿也不去了　好吗
Your mom is not going anywhere. Okay?
好吗　高兴吗
Yeah? Yeah?
-去把活干完　-好
- Go finish your chores. - Okay.
有人吗
Hello?
我是警察
Police officer out here.
能借点汽油吗
Can I borrow some gas?
有人吗
Hello?
有人吗　有人在家吗
Hello? Anybody home?
(上帝请宽恕我们)
放轻松　别紧张
Easy now, easy.
我不会伤害你
I'm not gonna hurt you.
不会动你一根汗毛
Nothing like that.
咱们打个商量吧
More like a proposal.
顺路南下就能到亚特兰大了
Atlanta's just down the road ways.
那里很安全
It's safe there.
包吃包住　有人　还有你的同类
Food, shelter, people, other horses too, I bet.
这主意怎么样
How's that sound?
套上了　真乖　真听话
There we go. Good boy. Good boy.
现在跟我走吧　跟着我
Now come with me. Come with me.
我们慢慢来　好吗
Let's go easy, ok?
我好几年没骑马了
I haven't done this for years.
别急　慢慢来　别急　慢点
Easy. Easy, boy. Easy, easy, easy.
镇定　几个而已　咱们有无敌马腿呢
Steady. It's just a few. Nothing we can't outrun.
那好吧
Okay.
洛莉　卡尔　对不起
Lori, Carl, I'm sorry.
你好
Hey, you.
你个白痴
Dumb ass.
就是你　躲坦克里的你
Hey, you in the tank.
里面还舒服吗
Cozy in there?